dreamscene.org 2017-12-16

# dreamscene.org - Privacy Policy

\- Privacy Policy:

**The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us.**

At dreamscene.org, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit dreamscene.org, and how we safeguard your information. 

If the opportunity for the input of personal or business data (email addresses, name, addresses) is given, the input of these data takes place voluntarily. The use of all offered services are permitted - if and so far technically possible and reasonable - without specification of any personal data or under specification of anonymized data or an alias. We never sell your personal information to third parties! 

**Log files**

Like many other Web sites, dreamscene.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

dreamscene.org does use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. If you wish to disable or selectively turn off cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites, or at [aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). 

We also use third party advertisements on dreamscene.org to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/). 

**Google AdSense (DoubleClick DART Cookie)**

Google, as a third party vendor, may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google's DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests ("interest based targeting"). 

You can find the Google AdSense Privacy Policy [here](http://google.com/privacy/ads/). 

The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses "non personally identifiable information". It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number or credit card numbers. 

You can opt-out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Google's Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). 

**Facebook (Facebook Social Plug-in):**

Our website uses so called Social Plugins („Plugins") of the social network facebook.com, which is operated by Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). The plugins are identifiable by one of the Facebook logos (white “f” on a blue background or a “thump-up” sign) or are identified by the phrase “Facebook Social Plugin”. The list and the look of Facebook Social Plugins can be found here: developers.facebook.com/plugins. 

Purpose and detail of the data assessment and the further use and analysis of the Data through Facebook and your thus related personal rights and control functions to protect your private data can be found in the data disclaimer of Facebook: [www.facebook.com/policy.php](http://www.facebook.com/policy.php). 

If you are a member of Facebook and do not want Facebook to collect your data via our website and stores it in relationship to your Facebook member account, you will need to log out of Facebook prior to the visit of our website and you may also have to delete any related cookies stored locally by Facebook. 

**Google Plus +1 button:**

Our website uses the "Google +1" button, which is operated by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States ("Google"). The button can be identified by the symbol "+1" on a white or colored background. 

When you visit a page of our website, which contains such a button, your browser will establish a direct link with the servers operated by Google. The content of the "+1" button will be directly transferred to your browser and embedded in the website being shown. We therefore have no effect on the amount of data collected, with the Google button. According to Google, without clicking on the button no personal data is collected. Only for logged in members such data, including the IP address, is collected and processed. To prevent this you must log out of your Google+ account before visiting our website. 

Please refer to Google+’s privacy policy for more information on the purpose and scope of data collection and data analysis made by Google+, your rights, how to modify settings and how to protect your privacy: <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

**Twitter social button (Twitter):**

This is a service supplied by Twitter, a company that complies with the Safe Harbor Privacy Policy Framework initiative, guaranteeing the handling of Personal Data in compliance with European security standards. By simply clicking on the Twitter push-button on the Site ("Twitter Button"), the service makes it possible to share liking of the Site on Twitter.com, without having to exit the Website’s page. In this way the User links his/her/its Twitter profile to the Website and makes this information accessible to anyone on the web. 

Place of Data Processing: USA More information: [twitter.com/privacy](http://twitter.com/privacy). 

The personal data collected are: Cookie and IP. 

\- Contact:

If you have any questions, complaints, suggestions, or feedback of any kind, please feel free to contact us: 

contact
